[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Just make sure there's no evidence.
A brokenhearted man and a grieving son who just couldn't take it anymore.
They'll all think the same thing.
You can't make a mistake.
No one will ever know.
End it well.
We already know who killed him.
So what's the problem?
Dad is gone. He can't tell us what he wants anymore.
So don't use his name to justify
something that you want to do.
You want me to kill Brother Mikoy?
If Sianong fails,
Carlota.
Don't talk to me.
We're done.
Sianong!
Let Carlota go.
No one's going to chase you.
Let her go.
-Carlota. -Run after him!
I'm still wondering how Agent Sianong did that.
Me too, I still can't understand.
I don't know why we have to guard him.
And why he had to betray us.
Remember, he likes to read that book-- What is it again?
Yes.
I still can't believe he did that.
What did you think?
I don't know.
Have you seen Sianong?
Ma'am, we've been here for a while, and we haven't seen him.
Alex.
He might have gone through here.
Let's go.
Stay here and let us know if you see him.
-Yes, ma'am. -Okay, ma'am.
Cocoy.
-Wake up. -Ouch!
Easy.
What happened?
Where's Sianong?
It was him.
He's the mole.
Where is he?
He escaped.
How about Mikoy?
He's with Alex.
They're after him.
Yes?
What happened?
Mikoy is still alive.
How?
I just got a little too complacent,
and there was also a lack of judgment on my end.
Maybe that's why they kind of outsmarted me.
A little?
Alex, go ahead.
I'll stay here for now. I'll follow you.
Okay.
They're after me.
Vicky!
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
I don't understand what you're saying.
After everything I've done for you, for this mission,
for your grand mission, Vicky.
Do you know what I did?
I fucked everything up for this mission.
I fucked over the agency.
I fucked over everyone who cared about me.
And you knew all the risks!
So what now?
That's it?
Was that all for nothing?
No one forced you.
You chose this.
Because you made me feel like I mattered, Vicky.
That I could take revenge for Alice.
That everything we were doing would lead to something.
That it would go somewhere,
and that I was part of all this.
You mattered
when you were still useful to me.
Vicky!
This is where it ends, Sianong.
No, Vicky.
Vicky.
Surrender now.
Come with us and face what you've done.
You have nowhere else to go.
Sianong, that's enough!
Alex!
Bok, that's enough!
Mom?
-We need to leave. -Why?
We're compromised.
How about Sianong?
We'll deal with him later.
What if he talks?
He already knows what will happen to him if he does.
Let's go. Get your things.
What now, Mikoy?
Sianong.
It doesn't have to end this way.
You're angry?
Think about Chiara.
Think about your father!
What?
you still can't hurt me?
That's enough, Bok!
I don't want to hurt you.
Oh, really? Huh?
Sianong!
Sianong! Hold on!
Why?
Why are you saving me?
What kind of question is that?!
Help me!
Hold on!
Sianong!
Bok.
There's no going back for me, Bok.
No! There is! Just hold on!
I know you two are my friends.
Right?
But I screwed you both.
That's enough!
Give me one of your hands. Reach it out to me, please!
Reach it out, Sianong!
Mikoy.
It's not too late for Chiara.
Chiara isn't the one who's responsible for all of this.
It's Vicky.
Vicky is behind all of this.
You two go to Italy!
Can you do that later, Sianong?
Hold on!
Sianong.
-Sianong. -Bok.
-Sianong, hold on. -But…
I'm tired.
Sianong!
Sianong, don't!
Don't do that!
Sianong!
I never thought Sianong's story would end like this.
I'm not used to it.
The silence.
No one's correcting us anymore.
No one's suddenly going to say, "According to the 7 habits."
Then it will lead to a 20-minute discussion.
And somehow end up talking about Lord of the Rings.
Everything somehow ends up with him talking about Lord of the Rings.
He always used to tell me
to think first.
Don't act rashly.
Follow the plan.
Follow the rules.
It's annoying.
He was always right.
That's why I don't understand
why he let things get that far.
We couldn't sleep last night either.
Agent Alex and I went through everything.
The records he was involved in.
Just to see where we went wrong,
what we missed.
Do you know about Sianong?
Imagine,
she already had someone inside GAGO,
And that's what worries us, dear.
We don't know who her contacts are,
or how she got in, right?
And who are the people working under her?
We have no idea.
Apparently, Sianong loved someone who became a victim of human trafficking.
And he wasn't able to save her.
He wasn't able to get justice for her either.
He never told me.
None of us knew.
But what Sianong did was wrong.
He betrayed us.
He tried to kill Mikoy.
But I don't want that to be what we remember him by.
Sianong was a good person.
He just lost his way.
I wish he had told us.
I wish he had given us a chance to help him.
But that doesn't justify betraying us.
It doesn't.
But that's the reason why Vicky was able to use him.
He was used as a weapon.
He was also a victim of a system that made him believe he had no other choice.
I'm not saying what he did was right.
But if we don't want what happened to Sianong to happen again,
we need to bring down the system
that creates people like him.
And the Concordat.
Dear.
If she can plant someone
inside GAGO,
then she can also plant someone
right beside you.
What?
Wherever he is now,
I hope he found the peace
he couldn't find here.
Before he let go, he told us something.
Let's go to Italy.
What's in Italy?
That's what we need to find out.
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
No contacts for Sianong there,
no accounts,
not even any recent travel records.
But he said it himself, Italy.
Maybe we're missing something.
Where's Carlota, by the way?
Thank you.
Looks like you ordered enough for an entire family.
Do you see a family here?
Do you want to talk about it?
No.
I'm such an idiot.
I knew you wanted to talk about it.
I don't understand.
We went on so many dates.
We talked about so many things.
I still don't know who he was.
Who he really was.
Some part of it must've been real.
Surely not all of it was a lie.
He liked to make plans.
Sianong?
He even made a list
of all the places he wanted to visit.
I even told him,
for our VL,
he might as well turn it into a project management plan.
What?
Definitely Italy.
What do you mean by that?
I thought you'd say New Zealand.
So what are you going to do in Italy?
So many things!
You already have an itinerary!
It's not an itinerary.
It's a preliminary plan!
That's even worse!
No. I have some friends there too.
Castellanis?
Fancy!
Don't worry.
One day, I'll take you there.
Really?
How about now!
Castellani.
What?
Castellani!
Hey, wait. Who's paying for this?
I've figured it out.
Carlota?
Now I know why in Italy.
Why?
Sianong has friends there.
The Castellanis.
Castellani?
The last thing he told me
was that he wanted to go to Italy because he wanted to visit them.
If that's Sianong's last clue to us,
those are the people he wants us to find.
I have news about the Castellani.
it's impossible that we can persuade her to come back to our country.
Didn't we agree to bring Chiara Valtrovi back?
What's the problem?
What did they say?
They wanted to meet me. ASAP.
You know those Castellanis. They are cunning.
They're cunning? That's their reputation.
We won't back out.
I know they are in Italy.
But Italy is too big, and I don't have enough time.
If I have to know something as soon as possible,
then tell me now.
Do not go, please.
I'm sure all of them are waiting to see how I will handle this.